Bonanza: The Return is a western, tv movie film directed by Jerry Jameson.
A man with a grudge against the late Little Joe seeks revenge on the
Cartwrights and attempts to take over the Ponderosa.
Bronc Evans, played by Ben Johnson.
Benjamin 'Benj' Cartwright, played by Michael Landon Jr..
Sara Cartwright, played by Emily Warfield.
Josh Cartwright, played by Brian Leckner.
Jacob Briscoe, played by Richard Roundtree.
Buckshot, played by Jack Elam.
Bonanza: The Return is a 1993 American Western  made-for-television film.
It is a sequel to both the 1959–1973 television series Bonanza and the
1988 made-for-television film Bonanza: The Next Generation.
The film was directed by Jerry Jameson and featured noted character actors Ben
Johnson, Jack Elam, Dean Stockwell, Linda Gray, and Richard Roundtree.
The film premiered on NBC on November 28, 1993.